const trivia = [
  {
    question: 'question1',
    options: ['answer1a', 'answer1b', 'answer1c', 'answer1d'],
    answer: 'answer1b',
  },
  {
    question: 'question2',
    options: ['answer2a', 'answer2b', 'answer2c', 'answer2d'],
    answer: 'answer2a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question3',
    options: ['answer3a', 'answer3b', 'answer3c', 'answer3d'],
    answer: 'answer3d',
  },
  {
    question: 'question4',
    options: ['answer4a', 'answer4b', 'answer4c', 'answer4d'],
    answer: 'answer4a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question5',
    options: ['answer5a', 'answer5b', 'answer5c', 'answer5d'],
    answer: 'answer5c',
  },
  {
    question: 'question6',
    options: ['answer6a', 'answer6b', 'answer6c', 'answer6d'],
    answer: 'answer6b',
  },
  {
    question: 'question7',
    options: ['answer7a', 'answer7b', 'answer7c', 'answer7d'],
    answer: 'answer7a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question8',
    options: ['answer8a', 'answer8b', 'answer8c', 'answer8d'],
    answer: 'answer8a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question9',
    options: ['answer9a', 'answer9b', 'answer9c', 'answer9d'],
    answer: 'answer9a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question10',
    options: ['answer10a', 'answer10b', 'answer10c', 'answer10d'],
    answer: 'answer10a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question11',
    options: ['answer11a', 'answer11b', 'answer11c', 'answer11d'],
    answer: 'answer11a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question12',
    options: ['answer12a', 'answer12b', 'answer12c', 'answer12d'],
    answer: 'answer12b',
  },
  {
    question: 'question13',
    options: ['answer13a', 'answer13b', 'answer13c', 'answer13d'],
    answer: 'answer13c',
  },
  {
    question: 'question14',
    options: ['answer14a', 'answer14b', 'answer14c', 'answer14d'],
    answer: 'answer14a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question15',
    options: ['answer15a', 'answer15b', 'answer15c', 'answer15d'],
    answer: 'answer15a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question16',
    options: ['answer16a', 'answer16b', 'answer16c', 'answer16d'],
    answer: 'answer16b',
  },
  {
    question: 'question17',
    options: ['answer17a', 'answer17b', 'answer17c', 'answer17d'],
    answer: 'answer17a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question18',
    options: ['answer18a', 'answer18b', 'answer18c', 'answer18d'],
    answer: 'answer18d',
  },
  {
    question: 'question19',
    options: ['answer19a', 'answer19b', 'answer19c', 'answer19d'],
    answer: 'answer19a',
  },
  {
    question: 'question20',
    options: ['answer20a', 'answer20b', 'answer20c', 'answer20d'],
    answer: 'answer20a',
  },
];

export default trivia;
